

**Robert Jach** 

Kraków phone: +48 508 339 994 robertjjach@gmail.com LinkedIn

Portfolio

# Languages

English - C1, Polish (native)

## **Proficencies**

Unity

**Unreal Engine** 

Adobe: (Photoshop, Illustrator)

Google (AdManager, Analytics)

Jira, ClickUp

## **Skills**

Level Design
Quest and Narrative Design
Level Art (2d/3d)
Game, Gameplay Design
Manual Testing
Creativity
Knowledge of the game industry
Ability to organize work independently

#### References

Gamesture - brozbicki@gamesture.com Gry-Online S.A. - michal.ramz@gmail.com Moonlit S.A. - siwek.maciek@gmail.com

## **Education**

Politechnika Krakowska

2009 - 2012

hydro-engineering

Krakowska Akademia im. Andrzeja Frycza

Modrzewskiego

T 2000

architecture

2005 - 2008

#### **Hobbies**

games (video, tabletop and roleplaying), horror movies, comic books, art, architecture, historical fencing

### **About me**

I am a **creative game and level** designer with an **analytical approach** to building levels. I am **organized and work well** with people in the team. I am **constantly improving** my **skills**, also by analyzing new titles and trends in the industry.

My goal is to create well-designed, memorable games. By materializing my ideas, I want to give players the best possible experience.

# **Experience**

07/2022 - 06/2024

**Level and quest designer -** project <u>Hero Legacy</u>, taken over from Gamesture. Hero Legacy won the best polish mobile game award at Digital Dragons 2024.

Boombit, Gdańsk; Gamesture, Kraków

- Level Design creating maps (levels), environmental puzzles, encounters, creating visual narration
- Quest Design creating quests and puzzles
- Narrative Design lore building, writing quest plots and dialogues
- Level Art creating game world through setting terrain, props, creating visual narration, maintaining thematic and visual coherency of game's world
- Game Design creating new gameplay mechanics in cooperation with dev
- **Testing** manual, for all of the game features.

09/2017 - 05/2022

# F2P promotion specialist, graphic designer GRY-Online S.A., Kraków

- Designing new features for the website, preparing design documents
- Designing and creating graphical assets and marketing content
- Acquiring customers and maintaining long-term relationships

02/2018 - 08/2018

**Game designer -** project Neon Noir **Moonlit S.A.**, Kraków

- Level Design Designing enemies, encounters and levels
- Narrative Design Writing lore and plot
- **Game Design** creating game mechanics
- Creating game design and reference documents for the project

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie danych osobowych zawartych w niniejszym dokumencie do realizacji procesu rekrutacji zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochronie danych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).